A mountain thief is a mountain thief.
سارق الجبال هو سارق الجبال.
You don't know anything about etiquette.
أنت لا تعرف أي شيء عن الإتيكيت.
Do you want me
هل تريدني
to teach you again?
ليعلمك مرة أخرى؟
Kneel down.
اركع للأسفل.
You look good. I wish
تبدو بخير.  أتمنى
you were younger.
كنت أصغر سنا.
General,
عام،
the person who ordered
الشخص الذي أمر
Toad Village is not here.
قرية العلجوم ليست هنا.
General, spare me.
جنرال ، وفر لي.
I still have
ما زلت أمتلك
a daughter to feed.
ابنة لتغذية.
Father,
أب،
Does this cushion work?
هل تعمل هذه الوسادة؟
This new cotton is a little soft.
هذا القطن الجديد ناعم قليلاً.
Prepare one for the boss, too,
قم بإعداد واحدة للرئيس أيضًا ،
Hey,
يا،
Where's the boss.
أين الرئيس.
I didn't expect Black Rock City
لم أكن أتوقع بلاك روك سيتي
to be so overbearing.
لتكون متعجرف جدا.
If you don't want to kneel,
إذا كنت لا تريد الركوع ،
just run away.
فقط اهرب.
If it were you,
لو كنت أنت
what would you choose?
فماذا تختار؟
If a man has gold under his knee,
إذا كان الرجل تحت ركبته ذهب ،
it's impossible to kneel.
من المستحيل الركوع.
If you want to escape,
إذا كنت تريد الهروب ،
in this troubled times,
في هذه الأوقات العصيبة ،
Will my brothers and I
هل أنا وإخوتي
just keep running away like this?
فقط استمر في الهرب هكذا؟
Oh,
أوه،
this is
هذا هو
the boss,
الرئيس،
If we don't leave now,
إذا لم نغادر الآن ،
I'm afraid there's no way out.
أخشى أنه لا يوجد مخرج.
How can there be so many things
كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك أشياء كثيرة
in this world that have a way out?
في هذا العالم الذي لديه مخرج؟
How sure are you?
كيف بالتأكيد أنت؟
Even if it's only 10%,
حتى لو كانت 10٪ فقط ،
I have to give it a try.
يجب أن أجربها.
Qin Man,
تشين مان
I didn't expect you to be greedy and afraid of death.
لم أكن أتوقع منك أن تكون جشعًا وخائفًا من الموت.
It's too late for you to dig a hole and run away.
لقد فات الأوان لكي تحفر حفرة وتهرب.
Gosh, I'll go.
يا إلهي ، سأذهب.
Master,
يتقن،
what is this thing for?
ما هذا الشيء؟
The secret must not be revealed.
يجب عدم الكشف عن السر.
This might be a lifeline for Toad Village.
قد يكون هذا شريان الحياة لقرية العلجوم.
Is this Toad Village?
هل هذه قرية العلجوم؟
Why didn't anyone come out?
لماذا لم يخرج أحد؟
Guys, listen up.
يا رفاق ، استمعوا.
Within 10 breaths,
في غضون 10 أنفاس ،
If the gate doesn't open,
إذا لم تفتح البوابة ،
break the door with me,
حطم الباب معي
One.
واحد.
how
كيف
I've figured it
لقد فهمت ذلك
out. Kneel down.
خارج.  اركع للأسفل.
General Lu, you're joking.
الجنرال لو ، أنت تمزح.
Why don't you kneel down and demonstrate,
لماذا لا تجثو وتتظاهر
How dare you tease me?
كيف تجرؤ على مضايقتي؟
Today, I'm going to bloodbath this Toad Village,
اليوم ، سأذهب إلى حمام دم في قرية العلجوم ،
Liang.
ليانغ.
This is.
هذا هو.
Lu Hum,
لو هوم
you're rebellious and belligerent,
أنت متمرد ومقاتل ،
Killing innocent people indiscriminately,
قتل الأبرياء دون تمييز ،
today my Toad Village is going to do justice for heaven,
اليوم سوف تقوم قرية العلجوم الخاصة بي بإنصاف الجنة ،
Brothers,
الإخوة،
kill and destroy the village,
اقتل ودمر القرية ،
Go.
يذهب.
Shoot!
أطلق النار!
You brat.
أنت شقي.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I once held the Book of Sages,
لقد حملت ذات مرة كتاب الحكماء ،
held the Sword of Green Blade,
أمسك سيف النصل الأخضر ،
I once thought about acquiring arts and culture,
فكرت ذات مرة في اكتساب الفنون والثقافة ،
goods and imperial family,
البضائع والأسرة الإمبراطورية ،
As far as I can see,
بقدر ما أستطيع أن أرى،
refugees are like pigs and dogs,
اللاجئون مثل الخنازير والكلاب ،
As powerful as a tiger and wolf,
بقوة النمر والذئب ،
at that time,
فى ذلك التوقيت،
I have an ideal,
لدي فكرة مثالية ،
to save the world from fire and water.
لإنقاذ العالم من النار والماء.
The relief of the people is upside down.
إغاثة الناس رأسا على عقب.
To seek justice for heaven and earth.
لطلب العدل للسماء والأرض.
Kneel down!
اركع!
Who on earth are you?
من أنت على وجه الأرض؟
Call me Toad King.
اتصل بي الملك العلجوم.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
Cheng Da Lei not only humiliated me, Jiang Lu Hum,
تشنغ دا لي لم يذلني فقط ، جيانغ لو هوم ،
How dare you write a letter to provoke you?
كيف تجرؤ على كتابة خطاب لاستفزازك؟
What a traitor.
يا له من خائن.
We must kill him.
يجب أن نقتله.
Knowing that there are tigers on the mountain,
مع العلم أن هناك نمورًا على الجبل ،
I prefer to go to Tiger Mountain.
أفضل الذهاب إلى جبل تايجر.
This guy is interesting,
هذا الرجل مثير للاهتمام ،